undeveloped.com 2016-04-22

# Privacy policy | Undeveloped

Through its online service, www.undeveloped.com will process privacy-sensitive or personal data. Undeveloped B.V. values the privacy of its customers and observes due care in processing and protecting personal data. 

We process data in compliance with the requirements laid down by the Dutch Personal Data Protection Act (DPDA). Undeveloped B.V. is the party responsible for all data processing. In this privacy statement, we will explain which personal data we collect and for which purposes. We recommend that you read it carefully. 

This privacy statement was last amended on 25 May 2015. 

##  Use of Personal Data 

By using our service, you are providing certain data to us. This could be personal data. We only retain and use the personal data provided directly by you or for which it is clear that it has been supplied to us to be processed. Although companies can make use of our website, company data is not covered by the DPDA. This privacy statement is primarily directed to those using the website as a private person or as an employee. 

We use the following data to process orders: 

  * Telephone number 
  * Billing address 
  * Email address 

##  Contact Form and Newsletter 

We have a newsletter to inform those interested of our products and/or services. Your email address will be added to the list of subscribers automatically. Each newsletter contains a link with which to unsubscribe from our newsletter. 

If you fill out a contact form on the website or send us an email, the data you provide will be retained for as long as is necessary depending on the nature of the form or the content of your email, to fully answer and correctly handle your message or email. 

We collect your: 

  * Telephone number
  * Email address

We may contact you for commercial purposes: 

  * by email 

Each individual message offers you the opportunity to unsubscribe. 

If necessary, we may collect your location data (GPS). If that is the case, you will be asked to grant consent beforehand. 

This location data and other data can also be stored and processed by the provider of the navigation/mapping software, such as Google Maps, but the data could also be used by for example Google or Apple itself. We have no control over their actions. We recommend that you read the applicable privacy statement of the provider in question. 

##  Registration 

Certain features of our service require you to register beforehand. After your registration we will retain your user name and the personal data you provided. We will retain this data so that you do not have to re-enter it every time you visit our website, to contact you in connection with the execution of the agreement, invoicing and payment, and to provide an overview of the products and services you have purchased from us. 

We will not provide the data linked to your user name to third parties, unless it is necessary for the execution of the agreement you concluded with us or if this is required by law. In the event of suspicion of fraud or misuse of our website we may hand over personal data to the entitled authorities. 

To register on our website we require the following data: 

  * your telephone number 
  * your email address 
  * your payment details 
  * your user name 
  * your profile photo 

Our portal gives you access to a management environment where you can change and save your settings. To access our online portal we require: 

  * your telephone number 
  * your email address 
  * your user name 
  * your profile photo 

##  Providing Data to Third Parties 

We may provide your data to our partners. These partners are for example payment processors and other parties that are involved in the execution of the agreement. 

This concerns the following personal data: 

  * your email address 
  * your payment details 

Our website features social media buttons. These buttons are used by the providers of these services to collect your personal data. 

##  Security 

We take security measures to reduce misuse of and unauthorised access to personal data. We do keep statistics on our website, giving us access to individual data. However, we only access individual data insofar as necessary for the purposes set out in this statement. 

##  Third-party Websites 

This statement is not applicable to third-party websites connected to this website through links. We cannot guarantee that these third parties will handle your personal data in a secure and careful manner. We recommend you read these websites’ privacy statements before making use of these websites. 

##  Changes to this Privacy Statement 

We reserve the right to modify this statement. We recommend that you review this statement regularly, so that you remain informed of any changes. 

##  Inspection and Modification of your Data 

You can always contact us if you have any questions regarding our privacy policy or wish to review, modify or delete your personal data.
